Mystic River Watershed Association Records MS055
Digital Collections and Archives, Tufts University
- General subject files, 1924 -- 1993; 1967 -- 1990; MS055.003; 23.65 Linear Feet
  - Combined sewer overflow project environmental impact report public hearing record and response to comments, 1982; MS055.003.009.00009 (Box 9)
  - Combined sewer overflow facilities plan draft "EID/EIR scope" sections A-B, 1989; MS055.003.009.00010 (Box 9)
  - Combined sewer overflow facilities plan "draft EID/EIR scope" sections C-K, appendix, 1989; MS055.003.009.00011 (Box 9)
  - Combined sewer overflow plan "technical memorandum B2-2: best management practices source control alternatives evaluation and ccreening", 1989; MS055.003.009.00012 (Box 9)
  - Combined sewer overflow plan "technical memorandum 2-1: planning area", 1988; MS055.003.009.00013 (Box 9)
  - Combined sewer overflow facilities plan "technical memorandum 2-4: goals for the protection of water quality from CSOs", 1988; MS055.003.009.00014 (Box 9)
  - Combined sewer overflow facilities plan "technical memorandum B2-3: stormwater management and sewer system optimization alternatives", 1989; MS055.003.009.00015 (Box 9)
  - Combined sewer overflow "technical memorandum B-1: chronic dry weather overflow problem areas", 1989; MS055.003.009.00016 (Box 9)
  - Combined sewer overflow facilities plan: final dry weather overflow control program, 1989; MS055.003.009.00017 (Box 9)
  - Combined sewer overflow "draft best interim best management practices report", 1989; MS055.003.009.00018 (Box 9)
  - Combined sewer overflow facilities plan: technical memorandum 8-3, 1989; MS055.003.009.00019 (Box 9)
  - Combined sewer overflow, MS055.003.009.00020 (Box 9)
  - Combined sewer overflow, 1975 -- 1984; MS055.003.009.00021 (Box 9)
  - Combined sewer overflow, 1989 -- 1990; MS055.003.009.00022 (Box 9)
  - Report on groundwater and surface study, 1978; MS055.003.009.00023 (Box 9)
  - Groundwater reports and information, 1983 -- 1984; MS055.003.009.00024 (Box 9)
  - Groundwater quality and protection, 1982; MS055.003.009.00025 (Box 9)
  - Groundwater protection strategy, 1983; MS055.003.009.00026 (Box 9)
  - Groundwater and groundwater law in Massachusetts, 1983; MS055.003.009.00027 (Box 9)
  - Groundwater and groundwater law in Massachusetts, 1976; MS055.003.009.00028 (Box 9)
  - Underground petroleum storage tanks: local regulation of a groundwater hazard", 1984; MS055.003.009.00029 (Box 9)
  - Groundwater protection: a guide for communities, 1982; MS055.003.009.00030 (Box 9)
  - Groundwater, 1973 -- 1981; MS055.003.009.00031 (Box 9)
  - Urban runoff flow regulators/concentrations, 1979; MS055.003.009.00032 (Box 9)
  - Cambridge, Massachusetts: the changing of a landscape, 1978; MS055.003.009.00033 (Box 9)
  - Program ideas, 1975 -- 1985; MS055.003.010.00001 (Box 10)
    First of two folders.
  - Program ideas, 1975 -- 1979; MS055.003.010.00002 (Box 10)
    Second of two.
  - Wildlife habitat, 1978; MS055.003.010.00003 (Box 10)
  - Wildlife, 1976 -- 1982; MS055.003.010.00004 (Box 10)
  - The birds of the Boston Public Library, 1921-1924, 1925; MS055.003.010.00005 (Box 10)
  - Publications index, 1979; MS055.003.010.00006 (Box 10)
  - Draft environmental impact report, Inwood Office Park, Woburn, Massachusetts, 1987; MS055.003.010.00007 (Box 10)
    First of two.
  - Draft environmental impact report, Inwood Office Park, Woburn, Massachusetts, 1987; MS055.003.010.00008 (Box 10)
  - Mystic River Watershed wildlife, 1977; MS055.003.010.00009 (Box 10)
  - Wildlife problems and studies, 1976 -- 1980; MS055.003.010.00010 (Box 10)
  - Tracings, MS055.003.010.00011 (Box 10)
  - Hawks and owls and mice, 1976; MS055.003.010.00012 (Box 10)
  - Transparencies, MS055.003.010.00013 (Box 10)
    Date not available
  - Neighborhood animals, 1976; MS055.003.010.00014 (Box 10)
  - Bird territories, techniques, 1972; MS055.003.010.00015 (Box 10)
  - Tree map, 1966; MS055.003.010.00016 (Box 10)
  - Draft environmental impact statement on the upgrading of the Boston Metropolitan Area sewerage system, volume 1, 1978; MS055.003.010.00017 (Box 10)
  - Effective citizen participation in transportation planning, 1976; MS055.003.010.00018 (Box 10)
  - Transportation facts for the Metropolitan Boston region, 1983; MS055.003.010.00019 (Box 10)
  - Transportation newsclippings, 1973 -- 1989; MS055.003.010.00020 (Box 10)
  - Transportation, technical, 1972 -- 1982; MS055.003.010.00021 (Box 10)
  - Transportation, technical, 1983 -- 1985; MS055.003.010.00022 (Box 10)
  - Transportation, technical, 1986 -- 1987; MS055.003.010.00023 (Box 10)
  - Transportation correspondence, 1971 -- 1986; MS055.003.010.00024 (Box 10)
  - Transportation - Joint Regional Transit Committee, 1950 -- 1982; MS055.003.010.00025 (Box 10)
  - Transportation, Joint Regional Transit Committee, 1988 -- 1990; MS055.003.010.00026 (Box 10)
  - Hydrologic study of the Mystic River Basin proposal, 1977; MS055.003.010.00027 (Box 10)
    One of two.
  - Hydrologic study of the Mystic River Basin proposal, 1977; MS055.003.010.00028 (Box 10)
    Two of two.
  - Water quality standards, 1990; MS055.003.011.00001 (Box 11)
  - Sewage sludge, 1976; MS055.003.011.00002 (Box 11)
  - Sediments, 1984; MS055.003.011.00003 (Box 11)
  - Recycling, 1975 -- 1982; MS055.003.011.00004 (Box 11)
  - Drinking water supply, 1976 -- 1985; MS055.003.011.00005 (Box 11)
  - Yacht and boat club, 1984; MS055.003.011.00006 (Box 11)
  - Hydrologic data of the coastal drainage basins of northeastern Massachusetts, from Castle Neck River, Ipswich, to Mystic River, Boston, 1980; MS055.003.011.00007 (Box 11)
  - Field trips, 1976; MS055.003.011.00008 (Box 11)
  - Sewer system, 1966 -- 1985; MS055.003.011.00009 (Box 11)
  - Mystic hydrology study, 1959 -- 1990; MS055.003.011.00010 (Box 11)
  - Wastewater and treatment, 1975 -- 1984; MS055.003.011.00011 (Box 11)
  - Hazardous wastes, 1979 -- 1990; MS055.003.011.00012 (Box 11)
  - Urban stormwater runoff citizen handbook, MS055.003.011.00013 (Box 11)
  - Infiltration/inflow, 1988; MS055.003.011.00014 (Box 11)
  - Draft executive summary combined sewer overflow facilities plan, 1989; MS055.003.011.00015 (Box 11)
  - Draft executive summary combined sewer overflow facilities plan, 1989; MS055.003.011.00016 (Box 11)
  - Stepan/Division of Water Pollution Control study, 1976 -- 1978; MS055.003.011.00017 (Box 11)
  - Local Growth Act, 1976; MS055.003.011.00018 (Box 11)
  - Trails and wildlife, 1967 -- 1972; MS055.003.011.00019 (Box 11)
  - Poisons and insect sprays, 1981 -- 1982; MS055.003.011.00020 (Box 11)
  - Massachusetts Watershed Coalition, 1980 -- 1981; MS055.003.011.00021 (Box 11)
  - Draft environmental impact report, combined sewer overflow facilities plan, volume 2 of 3, 1989; MS055.003.011.00022 (Box 11)
    Folder one of three.
  - Draft environmental impact report, combined sewer overflow facilities plan, volume 2 of 3, 1989; MS055.003.011.00023 (Box 11)
    Folder two of three.
  - Draft environmental impact report, combined sewer overflow facilities plan, volume 2 of 3, 1989; MS055.003.011.00024 (Box 11)
    Folder three of three.
  - Mill Brook hydraulic improvement study, 1980; MS055.003.011.00025 (Box 11)
  - Mill Brook hydrological flood plain study, 1974; MS055.003.011.00026 (Box 11)
    Folder one of two.
  - Mill Brook hydrological flood plain study, 1974; MS055.003.011.00027 (Box 11)
    Folder two of two.
  - The establishment and operation of the Aberjona River Commission, MS055.003.011.00028 (Box 11)
  - Hazardous waste management in Massachusetts, 1981; MS055.003.011.00029 (Box 11)
  - Combined sewer overflow report by Comptroller General, 1979; MS055.003.011.00030 (Box 11)
  - Figures 2.1-2.7, MS055.003.011.00031 (Box 11)
  - Mystic River Basin hydrology study phase 1 report, 1978; MS055.003.011.00032 (Box 11)
  - Mystic River Basin hydrology study phase 1 report, 1978; MS055.003.011.00033 (Box 11)
  - An analysis of water quality goals and objectives in the Boston Metropolitan Area: draft final report, 1977; MS055.003.012.00001 (Box 12)
  - An access oriented parking strategy for the Boston Metropolitan Area: final report, 1974; MS055.003.012.00002 (Box 12)
  - Soil, water, and related resources in the United States: status, condition, and trends: 1980 appraisal part 1, MS055.003.012.00003 (Box 12)
  - Soil, water, and related resources in the United States: status, condition, and trends: 1980 appraisal part 2, MS055.003.012.00004 (Box 12)
  - Draft areawide waste treatment management plan: part 1, volume 1, 1978; MS055.003.012.00005 (Box 12)
  - Draft areawide waste treatment management plan: part 1, volume 2, 1978; MS055.003.012.00006 (Box 12)
  - Draft areawide waste treatment management plan: part 1, volume 3, 1978; MS055.003.012.00007 (Box 12)
  - Draft areawide waste treatment management plan: part 2, 1978; MS055.003.012.00008 (Box 12)
  - A guide to understanding and administering the Massachusetts Wetlands Protection Act, 1977; MS055.003.012.00009 (Box 12)
  - A guide to understanding and administering the Massachusetts Wetlands Protection Act, 1977; MS055.003.012.00010 (Box 12)
    Second of two folders.
  - Massachusetts water quality standards, 1977; MS055.003.012.00011 (Box 12)
  - Proposal to provide engineering services for the Aberjona River and Upper Mystic Lake Urban Runoff Project, 1979; MS055.003.012.00012 (Box 12)
  - Recreation, 1967 -- 1984; MS055.003.012.00013 (Box 12)
  - Recreation brochures, 1967 -- 1990; MS055.003.012.00014 (Box 12)
  - Recreation brochures, MS055.003.012.00015 (Box 12)
  - Pollution, 1976 -- 1988; MS055.003.012.00016 (Box 12)
  - Pollution articles, 1981 -- 1982; MS055.003.012.00017 (Box 12)
  - Massachusetts scenic and recreational rivers, 1982; MS055.003.012.00018 (Box 12)
  - Massachusetts outdoors: draft statewide comprehensive outdoor recreation plan, 1978; MS055.003.012.00019 (Box 12)
  - Recreation and open space opportunities associated with water cleanup: Metropolitan Area part A, 1980; MS055.003.012.00020 (Box 12)
  - Recreation and open space opportunities associated with water cleanup: Metropolitan Area part B, 1980; MS055.003.012.00021 (Box 12)
  - Local growth policy statements, A-M, 1976; MS055.003.012.00022 (Box 12)
  - Local growth policy statements, M-W, 1976; MS055.003.012.00023 (Box 12)
  - Report of the southeastern New England study 2: Boston Metropolitan planning area report, 1975; MS055.003.012.00024 (Box 12)
  - EPA Regional Administrator's annual report: environmental quality in New England, 1980; MS055.003.012.00025 (Box 12)
  - Record of decision remedial alternative selection, Industri-plex, Woburn, Massachusetts, MS055.003.013.00001 (Box 13)
  - Guiding, 1977 -- 1983; MS055.003.013.00002 (Box 13)
  - Wetlands, 1971 -- 1982; MS055.003.013.00003 (Box 13)
  - Hydraulic survey of the Aberjona River and operation of the Aberjona River Commission, 1973; MS055.003.013.00004 (Box 13)
  - A case for the parkways, 1974; MS055.003.013.00005 (Box 13)
  - Public participation, 1975 -- 1987; MS055.003.013.00006 (Box 13)
  - Water quality reports, 1970 -- 1981; MS055.003.013.00007 (Box 13)
  - Non-point pollution, 1987; MS055.003.013.00008 (Box 13)
  - Government policy and programs, 1977; MS055.003.013.00009 (Box 13)
  - Road salt, 1971 -- 1976; MS055.003.013.00010 (Box 13)
  - Fox, 1973 -- 1980; MS055.003.013.00011 (Box 13)
  - Liquid natural gas, 1976; MS055.003.013.00012 (Box 13)
  - Heavy metals, 1983 -- 1989; MS055.003.013.00013 (Box 13)
  - Land use conservation, 1966 -- 1976; MS055.003.013.00014 (Box 13)
  - Metropolitan Area Planning Council, 1978 -- 1990; MS055.003.013.00015 (Box 13)
  - Proposed regulations to implement the Public Waterfront Act (Chapter 91): introduction and summary, 1989; MS055.003.013.00016 (Box 13)
  - Northeastern United States water supply, 1977; MS055.003.013.00017 (Box 13)
  - Citizens' handbook to the 3C transportation planning process in Massachusetts, MS055.003.013.00018 (Box 13)
  - The importance of citizen participation and consensus building in the land use planning program, 1977; MS055.003.013.00019 (Box 13)
  - Red Line extension land use study, 1990; MS055.003.013.00020 (Box 13)
  - Hazardous materials in the Metropolitan Area Planning Council Region: locations, movements, regulations, 1979; MS055.003.013.00021 (Box 13)
  - Massachusetts water supply policy study, 1979; MS055.003.013.00022 (Box 13)
    Chapters 1-6.
  - Massachusetts water supply policy study, 1979; MS055.003.013.00023 (Box 13)
    Chapter 7 and Appendices.
  - Federal Water Pollution Control Act, 1977; MS055.003.013.00024 (Box 13)
  - Annotated itinerary, October 2 field trip (Woburn), MS055.003.013.00025 (Box 13)
  - Regulations for the disposal of solid waste by sanitary landfill: public discussion draft, 1983; MS055.003.013.00026 (Box 13)
  - Analysis of urban stormwater runoff and combined sewer overflows in the Boston Metropolitan Area, MS055.003.013.00027 (Box 13)
  - Incomplete report concerning town of Woburn, MS055.003.013.00028 (Box 13)
  - Combined sewer overflow facilities plan appendices: reference maps, 1988; MS055.003.013.00029 (Box 13)
    First of three folders.
  - Combined sewer overflow facilities plan appendices: reference maps, 1988; MS055.003.013.00030 (Box 13)
    Second of three.
  - Combined sewer overflow facilities plan appendices: reference maps, 1988; MS055.003.013.00031 (Box 13)
    Third of three.
  - Final areawide waste treatment management plan environmental impact statement for the Metropolitan Boston Area, 1978; MS055.003.014.00001 (Box 14)
  - Alewife Center: draft environmental impact report volume 1, 1986; MS055.003.014.00002 (Box 14)
  - Alewife Center: draft environmental impact report volume 2: technical appendices, 1986; MS055.003.014.00003 (Box 14)
  - Alewife Center: final environmental impact report volume 1, 1987; MS055.003.014.00004 (Box 14)
  - Revised draft, regional open space plan, vol. 1, 1975; MS055.003.014.00005 (Box 14)
  - Arlington open space study, 1972; MS055.003.014.00006 (Box 14)
  - Acid rain and related air pollutant damage, 1984; MS055.003.014.00007 (Box 14)
  - Private well contamination in Massachusetts: sources, responses, and needs, 1988; MS055.003.014.00008 (Box 14)
  - Reeds Brok Estates, Summer Street, Arlington, MA, 1985; MS055.003.014.00009 (Box 14)
    First of four folders.
  - Reeds Brok Estates, Summer Street, Arlington, MA, 1985; MS055.003.014.00010 (Box 14)
    Second of four folders.
  - Reeds Brok Estates, Summer Street, Arlington, MA, 1985; MS055.003.014.00011 (Box 14)
    Third of four folders.
  - Reeds Brok Estates, Summer Street, Arlington, MA, 1985; MS055.003.014.00012 (Box 14)
    Fourth of four folders.
  - Wells G and H wetlands assessment: final report, 1986; MS055.003.014.00013 (Box 14)
  - Wells G and H wetlands remedial investigation part 2: final report, 1986; MS055.003.014.00014 (Box 14)
  - Area of Influence and zone of cContribution to Superfund site wells G and H, Woburn, Mass., 1987; MS055.003.014.00015 (Box 14)
  - Addendum to Mystic River Basin preliminary report, MS055.003.014.00016 (Box 14)
  - The Mystic River Basin report action handbook and summary, 1977; MS055.003.014.00017 (Box 14)
  - Demonstration of nonpoint pollution abatement through improved street-cleaning practices, 1974; MS055.003.014.00018 (Box 14)
  - Draft environmental impact statement: downtown Malden general neighborhood renewal plan area and the industrial park urban renewal area, 1974; MS055.003.014.00019 (Box 14)
  - Planning for urban runoff control: financial and institutional issues (draft), 1981; MS055.003.014.00020 (Box 14)
  - Report on groundwater and surface water study, 1978; MS055.003.014.00021 (Box 14)
  - Nonpoint source stream nutrient level relationships, 1977; MS055.003.014.00022 (Box 14)
  - Land use planning and controls, 1975; MS055.003.015.00001 (Box 15)
  - Land use planning and controls, 1971 -- 1986; MS055.003.015.00002 (Box 15)
  - Bluebird, 1989; MS055.003.015.00003 (Box 15)
  - Water supply coordinator's meeting notes, 1976 -- 1977; MS055.003.015.00004 (Box 15)
  - Pamphlets, MS055.003.015.00005 (Box 15)
  - Public communications, 1976 -- 1985; MS055.003.015.00006 (Box 15)
  - Water quality, 1975 -- 1981; MS055.003.015.00007 (Box 15)
  - Task 3: Demand management summary report, 1983; MS055.003.015.00008 (Box 15)
  - Proceedings of seminar sessions on state water supply planning, 1975; MS055.003.015.00009 (Box 15)
  - Water supply, 1968 -- 1983; MS055.003.015.00010 (Box 15)
  - Water supply, 1984 -- 1990; MS055.003.015.00011 (Box 15)
  - Wetlands Protection Act regulations, 1983; MS055.003.015.00012 (Box 15)
  - Eastern Massachusetts Metropolitan Area study: main report, 1976; MS055.003.016.00001 (Box 16)
    - Fig. 1-1 EMMA Study Area Location, 1976; MS055.003.016.00001.00001 (Box 16)
      This illustration is from Metcalf & Eddy, Inc., "Eastern Massachusetts Metropolitan Area study: main report, 1976"
      Maps
    - Fig. 2-1 Existing MSD System, 1976; MS055.003.016.00001.00002 (Box 16)
    - Fig. 2-2 Combined Sewer Areas and Major Overflows, 1976; MS055.003.016.00001.00003 (Box 16)
    - Fig. 3-1 Projected Population and Employment Trends - 1970 to 2050 - EMMA Area, 1976; MS055.003.016.00001.00004 (Box 16)
      Figures (representations)
    - Fig. 3-2 Treatment Plant Service Areas and Major Projects in the Recommended Plan, 1976; MS055.003.016.00001.00005 (Box 16)
    - Fig. 3-3 Procedure for Project Implementation, 1976; MS055.003.016.00001.00006 (Box 16)
  - Eastern Massachusetts Metropolitan Area study technical data vol. 1: planning criteria, 1975; MS055.003.016.00002 (Box 16)
  - Eastern Massachusetts Metropolitan Area study technical data vol. 2: engineering criteria, 1975; MS055.003.016.00003 (Box 16)
  - Eastern Massachusetts Metropolitan Area study technical data vol. 3: industrial process wastewater analysis and regulation, 1975; MS055.003.016.00004 (Box 16)
  - Eastern Massachusetts Metropolitan Area study technical data vol. 3a: study of certain industrial wastes, 1975; MS055.003.016.00005 (Box 16)
  - Eastern Massachusetts Metropolitan Area study technical data vol. 3b: study of wastes from Large industries, 1975; MS055.003.016.00006 (Box 16)
  - Eastern Massachusetts Metropolitan Area study technical data vol. 4: water oriented wastewater utilization concepts, 1975; MS055.003.016.00007 (Box 16)
  - Eastern Massachusetts Metropolitan Area study technical data vol. 5: land oOriented wastewater utilization concepts, 1975; MS055.003.016.00008 (Box 16)
  - Eastern Massachusetts Metropolitan Area study technical data vol. 6: formulation of wastewater utilization plan, 1975; MS055.003.016.00009 (Box 16)
  - Eastern Massachusetts Metropolitan Area study technical data vol. 7: combined sewer overflow regulation, 1975; MS055.003.016.00010 (Box 16)
  - Eastern Massachusetts Metropolitan Area study technical data vol. 8: urban stormwater management, 1975; MS055.003.016.00011 (Box 16)
  - Eastern Massachusetts Metropolitan Area study technical data vol. 8a: appendix to urban stormwater management, 1975; MS055.003.016.00012 (Box 16)
  - Eastern Massachusetts Metropolitan Area study technical data vol. 9: Metropolitan District Commission interceptor and pumping station analysis and improvements, 1975; MS055.003.016.00013 (Box 16)
  - Eastern Massachusetts Metropolitan Area study technical data vol. 10: Deer Island wastewater treatment plant analysis and improvements, 1975; MS055.003.016.00014 (Box 16)
  - Eastern Massachusetts Metropolitan Area study technical data vol. 11: Nut Island wastewater treatment plant analysis and improvements, 1975; MS055.003.016.00015 (Box 16)
  - Eastern Massachusetts Metropolitan Area study technical data vol. 12: financing and management part 1, 1975; MS055.003.016.00016 (Box 16)
  - Eastern Massachusetts Metropolitan Area study technical data vol. 12: financing and management part 2, 1975; MS055.003.016.00017 (Box 16)
  - Eastern Massachusetts Metropolitan Area study technical data vol. 13: Impact and Evaluation, 1975; MS055.003.016.00018 (Box 16)
  - Eastern Massachusetts Metropolitan Area study technical data vol. 13a: biological impact analysis, 1975; MS055.003.016.00019 (Box 16)
  - Eastern Massachusetts Metropolitan Area study technical data vol. 13b: socio-economic impact analysis, 1975; MS055.003.016.00020 (Box 16)
  - Eastern Massachusetts Metropolitan Area study technical data vol. 13c: hygenic impact analysis, 1975; MS055.003.016.00021 (Box 16)
  - Eastern Massachusetts Metropolitan Area study technical data vol. 13d: visual, cultural, and design impact analysis, 1975; MS055.003.016.00022 (Box 16)
  - Eastern Massachusetts Metropolitan Area study technical data vol. 14: public involvement, 1975; MS055.003.016.00023 (Box 16)
  - Eastern Massachusetts Metropolitan Area study technical data vol. 15: recommended plan and implementation program, 1975; MS055.003.016.00024 (Box 16)
  - Eastern Massachusetts Metropolitan Area study report, 1975; MS055.003.016.00025 (Box 16)
  - Facilities plan for Millbrook Valley sewer, 1981; MS055.003.016.00026 (Box 16)
  - Facilities plan for Millbrook Valley sewer, 1981; MS055.003.016.00027 (Box 16)
    Second of three folders.
  - Facilities plan for Millbrook Valley sewer, 1981; MS055.003.016.00028 (Box 16)
    Third of three folders.
  - Preliminary hydrology study in the Alewife corridor, 1975; MS055.003.017.00001 (Box 17)
  - Areawide water quality management alternatives: final draft, 1976; MS055.003.017.00002 (Box 17)
  - Proposal to study feasible alternatives of correcting the flooding condition of Alewife Brook for the Alewife Task Force, 1976; MS055.003.017.00003 (Box 17)
  - Continued planning process for water quality mManagement in Massachusetts, 1977; MS055.003.017.00004 (Box 17)
  - Identification, delineation, and mapping of wetland areas for the Town of Arlington, 1974; MS055.003.017.00005 (Box 17)
  - Combined sewer overflow summary report, 1982; MS055.003.017.00006 (Box 17)
  - Draft environmental impact statement on the upgrading of the Boston Metropolitan Area sewerage system: executive summary, 1978; MS055.003.017.00007 (Box 17)
  - Water resources protection techniques, 1978; MS055.003.017.00008 (Box 17)
  - Comprehensive drainage study: Munroe Brook, Lexington, Mass., 1977; MS055.003.017.00009 (Box 17)
  - Watershed Associations Boston area needs, 1972; MS055.003.017.00010 (Box 17)
  - Mystic Center, Medford, Mass., final supplemental environmental impact report, 1988; MS055.003.017.00011 (Box 17)
  - Mystic Center, Medford, Mass., final supplemental environmental impact report, 1988; MS055.003.017.00012 (Box 17)
  - Mystic Center, Medford, Mass., final supplemental environmental impact report, 1988; MS055.003.017.00013 (Box 17)
  - Boston urban study, preliminary draft, 1973; MS055.003.017.00014 (Box 17)
  - Boston urban study, preliminary draft, 1973; MS055.003.017.00015 (Box 17)
  - List of confirmed disposal sites and locations to be investigated, 1988; MS055.003.017.00016 (Box 17)
  - Water supply-wastewater treatment coordination study, 1979; MS055.003.017.00017 (Box 17)
  - The nation's water, 1986; MS055.003.017.00018 (Box 17)
  - Small navigation project: Island End River, Chelsea, Mass., 1981; MS055.003.017.00019 (Box 17)
  - Small navigation project: Island End River, Chelsea, Mass., 1981; MS055.003.017.00020 (Box 17)
  - Cambridgepark phase 2: final environmental impact report, 1986; MS055.003.017.00021 (Box 17)
  - Red Line extension, Harvard Square to Arlington Heights: final environmental impact report statement, 1977; MS055.003.017.00022 (Box 17)
  - Environmental overview summary update: proposed railway improvements in the Alewife Corridor of Cambridge, Arlington, and Belmont, Mass., 1977; MS055.003.017.00023 (Box 17)